Allan M. Cormack Papers MS018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Papers by other scientists, 1931 -- 1990; MS018.007; 1.2 Linear Feet
  Gore, J. C. and S. Leeman. "The Reconstruction of Objects from Incomplete Projections." Physics in Medicine and Biology 25/1 (1980): 129-36.
  Green, John W. "On the Determination of a Function in the Plane by Its Integrals Over Straight Lines." Proceedings American Mathematical Society 9 (1958): 758-62.
  Greenberg, J. Mayo. "Scattering by Nonspherical Particles." Journal of Applied Physics 31/1 (January 1960): 82-84.
  Grosjean, Carl C. "Solution of the Non-Isotropic Random Flight Problem in the k-Dimensional Space." Physica XIX (1953): 29-45.
  Haimson, J. "X-Ray Source Without Moving Parts for Ultra-High Speed Tomography." IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science NS-26/2 (April 1979): 2857-61.
  Hamaker, C., K. T. Smith, D. C. Solmon, and S. L. Wagner. "The Divergent Beam X-Ray Transform." Rocky Mountain Journal of Mathematics 10/1 (Winter 1980): 253-83.
  Hansen, Eric W. "Circular Harmonic Image Reconstruction: Experiments." Applied Optics 20/13 (July 1, 1981): 2266-74.
  Hansen, Eric W. "Theory of Circular Harmonic Image Reconstruction." Journal of the Optical Society of America 71/3 (March 1981): 304-08.
  Hanson, K. M., J. N. Bradbury, T. M. Cannon, R. L. Hutson, D. B. Laubacher, R. J. Macek, M. A. Paciotti, and C. A. Taylor. "Computed Tomography Using Proton Energy Loss." Physics of Medicine and Biology 26/6 (1981): 965-83.
  Hanson, K. M., J. N. Bradbury, R. A. Koeppe, R. J. Macek, D. R. Machen, R. Morgado, M. A. Paciotti, S. A. Sandford, and V. W. Steward. "Proton Computed Tomography of Human Specimens." Physics of Medicine and Biology 27/1 (1982): 25-36.
  Hanson, Kenneth M. and George W. Wecksung. "Bayesian Approach to Limited-Angle Reconstruction in Computed Tomography." Journal of the Optical Society of America 73 (November 1983): 1501-09.
  Hayward, Evans and E. G. Fuller. "Photon Self-Absorption and Scattering by the 14.1-MeV Level in C12." The Physical Review 106/5 (June 1, 1957): 991-95.
  Hazou, I. A. and D. C. Salmon. "Approximate Inversion Formulas and Convulution Kernels for the Exponential X-Ray Transform." Zeitschrift fur Angewandte Mathematik und Mechanik 66 (1986): T370-72.
  Herman, G. T. "Convolution Reconstruction Techniques for Divergent Beams." Comput. Biol. Med. 6 (1976): 259-71.
  Herman, G. T. "A Relaxation Method for Reconstructing Objects from Noisy X-Rays." Mathematical Programming 8 (1975): 1-19.
  Herman, G. T., A. V. Lakshminarayanan, and S. W. Rowland. "The Reconstruction of Objects from Shadowgraphs with High Contrasts." Pattern Recognition 7 (1975): 157-65.
  Hertle, Alexander. "A Characterization of Fourier and Radon Transforms on Euclidean Space." Transactions of the American Mathematical Society 273/2 (October 1982): 595-607.
  Hertle, Alexander. "Continuity of the Radon Transform and Its Inverse on Euclidean Space." Mathematische Zeitschrift 184 (1983): 165-92.
  Hertle, Alexander. "On the Injectivity of the Attentuated Radon Transform." Proceedings of the American Mathematical Society 92/2 (October 1984): 201-05.
  Hertle, Alexander. "On the Range of the Radon Transform and Its Dual." Mathematische Annalen 267 (1984): 91-99.
  Higgins, Theodore P. "An Inversion Integral for a Gegenbauer Thransformation." Journal of the Society of Industrial Applications of Mathematics 11/4 (December 1963): 886-93.
  Hillman, Peter, A. Johansson, and H. Tyren. "Polarization of High Energy Protons in Elastic and Inelastic Scattering." Nuclear Physics 4/5 (1957): 648-61.
  Horn, Berthold K. P. "Density Reconstruction Using Arbitrary Ray-Sampling Schemes." Proceedings of the IEEE 66/5 (May 1978): 551-62.
  Horn, Berthold K. P. "Fan-Beam Reconstruction Methods." Proceedings of the IEEE 67/12 (December 1979): 1616-23.
  Horsman, A., D. H. Reading, J. Connolly, E. Bateman, W. Glasgow, and M. S. F. McLachlan. "Bone Mass Measurement Using a Xenon-Filled Multiwire Proportional Counter as Detector." Physics of Medicine and Biology 22/6 (1977): 1059-72.
  Hounsfield, Godfrey N. "Method of and Apparatus for Examining a Body by Radiation Such as X or Gamma Radiation." Canadian Patent 887891 (December 7, 1971).
  Hounsfield, Godfrey Newbold. "Method and Apparatus for Measuring X- or Gamma-Radiation Absorption or Transmission at Plural Angles and Analyzing the Data." United States Patent 3,778,614 (December 11, 1974).
  Houtermans, F. G. and W. Thirring. "Zur freien Weglange von Neutrinos." Helvetica Physica Acta 27/2 (1954): 81-88.
  Inouye, Tamon. "Image Reconstruction with Limited Angle Projection Data." IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science NS-26/2 (April 1979): 2666-96.
  James, R. W. and E. M. Firth. "An X-Ray Study of the Heat Motions of the Atoms in a Rock-Salt Crystal." Proceedings of the Royal Society, A, vol. 117 (1927): 62-87.
  Jelley, J. V. "Detection of Mu-Mesons and other Fast Charged Particles in Cosmic Radiation, by the Cerenkov Effect in Distilled Water." Proceedings of the Physical Society, A. vol. LXIV (1951): 82-87.
  Johnston, L. H. and D. A. Swenson. "Proton-Proton Scattering at 40 MeV." The Physical Review 3/1 (July 1, 1958): 212-22.
  Jones, L. K. and V. Trutzer. "Computationally Feasible High-Resolution Minimum-Distance Procedures Which Extend the Maximum-Entropy Method." Inverse Problems 5 (1999): 749-66.
  Juritz, J. W. F. "Cosmic-Ray Bursts and Shower Spread Under Large Thicknesses of Lead." Proceedings of the Royal Society, A., vol. 190 (1947): 426-34.
  Kak, Avinash C., Charles V. Jakowatz, Jr., Norman A. Bailey, and Robert A. Keller. "Computerized Tomography Using Video Recorded Fluoroscopic Images." IEEE Transactions on Biomedical Engineering BME-24/2 (March 1977): 157-69. Kershaw, D. "The Determination of the Density Distribution of a Gas Flowing in a Pipe from Mean Density Measurements." J. Inst. Maths Applics 6 (1970): 111-14.
  Klug, A. and R. A. Crowther. "Three-Dimensional Image Reconstruction from the Viewpoint of Information Theory." Nature 238 (August 25, 1972): 435-40.
  Kohler, T. R. and William Parrish. "X-Ray Diffractometry of Radioactive Samples." The Review of Scientific Instruments 26/4 (April 1955): 374-79.
  Kontrym-Sznajd, G. and J. Majsnerowski, "Electron-Positron Pair Momentum Densities in Mg and Cd." Solid State Communications 70/6 (1989): 593-97.
  Kosarev, E. L. "Applications of Integral Equations of the First Kind in Experimental Physics." Computer Physics Communications 20 (1980): 69-75.
  Kubo, Hayao and Ryo Nagata. "Determination of Dielectric Tensor Fields in Weakly Inhomogeneous Aisotropic Media." Journal of the Optical Society of America 69/4 (April 1979): 604-10.
  Kuckes, A. F., Richard Wilson, and Paul F. Cooper, Jr. "On the Deuteron as a Free Nucleon Target at 145 MeV." Annals of Physics 15 (1961): 193-222.
  Kumar, Anil, Dieter Welti, and Richard R. Ernst. "NMR Fourier Zeugmatography." Journal of Magnetic Resonance 18 (1975): 69-83.
  Lai, Ching-Ming and Paul C. Lauterbur. "Automatic Correction of Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Zeugmatographic Projections." Journal of Physics E: Scientific Instruments 14 (1981): 874-79.
  Lai, Ching-Ming and Paul C. Lauterbur. "A Gradient Control Device for Complete Three-Dimensional Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Zeugmatographic Imaging." Journal of Physics E: Scientific Instruments 13 (1980): 747-50.
  Lauterbur, Paul C. "Medical Imaging by Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Zeugmatography." IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science NS-26/2 (April 1979): 2808-11.
  Lewitt, Robert M. "Processing of Incomplete Measurement Data in Computed Tomography." Medical Physics 6/5 (September/October 1979): 412-17.
  Lind, Bengt K. "Properties of an Algorithm for Solving the Inverse Problem in Radiation Therapy." Inverse Problems 6 (1990): 415-426.
  Llacer, Jorge. "Theory of Imaging with a Very Limited Number of Projections." IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science NS-26/1 (February 1979): 596-602.
  Logan, B. F. "The Uncertainty Principle in Reconstructing Functions from Projections." Duke Mathematical Journal 42/4 (December 1975): 661-707.
  Logan, B. F. and L. A. Shepp. "Optimal Reconstruction of a Function from Its Projections." Duke Mathematical Journal 42/4 (December 1975): 645-59.
  Louis, A. K. "Ghosts in Tomography--The Null Space of the Radon Transform." Mathematical Methods in the Applied Sciences 3 (1981): 1-10.
  Louis, Alfred K. "Nonuniqueness in Inverse Radon Problems: The Frequency Distribution of the Ghosts." Mathematische Zeitschrift 185 (1984): 429-40.
  Louis, Alfred K. "Optimal Sampling in Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR) Tomography." Journal of Computer Assisted Tomography 6/2 (1982): 334-40.
  Louis, Alfred K. "Orthogonal Function Series Expansions and the Null Space of the Radon Transform." Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics Journal of Mathematical Analysis 15/3 (May 1984): 621-33.
  Madych, W. R. and S. A. Nelson. "Spherical Quadrature and Inversion of Radon Transforms." Proceedings of the American Mathematical Society 95/3 (November 1985): 453-57.
  Mann, A. K. "Elastic Scattering of Gamma Rays." The Physical Review, 101/1 (January 1, 1956): 4-8.
  Mansfield, P. and I. L. Pykett. "Biological and Medical Imaging by NMR." Journal of Magnetic Resonance 29 (1978): 355-73.
  Maris, Th. A. J., Peter Hillman, and H. Tyren. "Quasi-Electric Scattering and Nuclear Structure." Nuclear Physics 7/1 (1958): 1-9.
  Maris, Th. A. J. and H. Tyren. "Inelastic High Energy Nucleon Scattering on Light Nuclei." Nuclear Physics 3/1 (1957): 35-51.
  Maris, Th. A. J. and H. Tyren. "Some Remarks Concerning Measurements on Inelastic Scattering of 155-185 MeV Protons on Carbon, Oxygen and Calcium." Nuclear Physics 4/5 (1957): 662-71.
  Marr, Robert B. "On the Reconstruction of a Function on a Circular Domain from a Sampling of Its Line Integrals." Journal of Mathematical Analysis and Applications 45/2 (February 1974): 357-74.
  McCauley, G. P. and G. E. Brown. "Inelastic Scattering of High Energy Nucleons by Complex Nuclei I: Semi-Classical Formalism." Proceedings of the Physical Society, vol. LXXI (1958): 893-903.
  Mersereau, Russell M., Alan V. Oppenheim. Digital Reconstruction of Multidimensional Signals from Their Projections." Proceedings of the IEEE 62/10 (October 1974): 1319-38.
  Messelt, S. and A. Storruste. "Elastic Scattering of Gamma Rays." Proceedings of the Physical Society, A, Vol. LXIX (1956): 381-87.
  Metzger, Franz R. "Nuclear Resonance Fluorescence in Ge72 and Ge74." The Physical Review 101/1 (January 1, 1956): 286-94.
  Metzger, Franz R. "Nuclear Resonance Fluorescence in Ni60." The Physical Review 103/4 (August 15, 1956): 983-87.
  Metzger, Franz R. "Nuclear Resonance Fluorescence in Some Heavy Nuclei." Journal of the Franklin Institute 261/2 (February 1956): 219-36.
  Mohr, C. B. O and G. H. Stafford. "The Production of Cosmic-Ray Bursts by Mesotrons." Proceedings of the Royal Society, A, vol. 183 (1944): 54-64.
  Muller, H. R., R. Wuthrich, R. Hunig, M. Elke, and A. v. Hochstetter. "A Graphical Reporting System for computerized Axial x-Ray Tomography (EMI Scanning)." European Neurology 11 (1974): 197-207.
  Natterer, Frank. "Computerized Tomography with Unknown Sources." Society of Industrial and Applied Mathematics Journal of Applied Mathematics 43/5 (1983): 1201-12.
  Natterer, Frank. "Numerical Inversion of the Radon Transform." Numerische Mathematik 30 (1978): 81-91.
  Natterer, Frank. "On the Inversion of the Attenuated Radon Transform." Numerische Mathematik 32 (1979): 431-38.
  Nijboer, B. R. A. "The Diffraction Theory of Optical Aberrations." Physica 13/10 (December 1947): 605-20.
  Norton, Stephen J. "Mossbauer Imaging." Nature 330 (November 12, 1987): 151-53.
  Noyes, H. Pierre and Malcolm H. MacGregor. "Analysis of 40-MeV p-p Scattering." The Physical Review 3/1 (July 1, 1958): 223-27.
  Oberlin, D. M. and E. M. Stein, "Mapping Properties of the Radon Transform." Indiana University Mathematics Journal 31/5 (1982): 641-50.
  Oliker, V. I. "Near Radially Symmetric Solutions of an Inverse Problem in Geometric Optics." Inverse Problems 3 (1987): 743-56.
  Oliker, V. I. "On Reconstructing a Reflecting Surface from the Scattering Data in the Geometric Optics Approximation." Inverse Problems 5 (1989): 51-65.
  Palmieri, J. N. and Janet P. Wolfe. "Neutron-Proton Scattering at 152 MeV." Physical Review C, Nuclear Physics 3/1 (January 1971): 144-48.
  Papoulis, A. "Optical Systems, Singularity Functions, Complex Hankel Transforms," Journal of the Optical Society of America 57/2 (February 1967): 207-13.
  Perry, R. Michael. "On Reconstructing a Function on the Exterior of a Disk from Its Radon Transform." Journal of Mathematical Analysis and Applications 59 (1977): 324-41.
  Prigogine, I. and F. Henin. "Motion of a Relativistic Charged Particle." Physics 28 (1962): 667-88.
  Quinto, Eric Todd. "The Dependence of the Generalized Radon Transform on Defining Measures." Transactions of the American Mathematical Society 257 (February 1980): 331-46.
  Quinto, Eric Todd. "The Invertibility of Rotation Invariant Radon Transforms." Journal of Mathematical Analysis and Applications 91/2 (February 1983): 510-22.
  Quinto, Eric Todd. "Null Spaces and Ranges for the Classical and Spherical Radon Transforms." Journal of Mathematical Analysis and Applications 90/2 (December 1982): 408-20.
  Quinto, Eric Todd. "Tomographic Reconstruction from Incomplete Data--Numerical Inversion of the Exterior Radon Transform." Inverse Problems 4 (1988): 867-76.
  Quinto, Eric Todd. "Topological Restrictions on Double Fibrations and Radon Transforms." Proceedings of the American Mathematical Society 81/4 (April 1981): 570-74.
  Ramachandran, G. N. "Reconstruction of Substance from Shadow." Proceedings of the Indian Academy of Sciences, Section B, vol. LXXIVJ, no. 1: 14-24.
  Ramachandran, G. N. and A. V. Lakshminarayanan. "Three-Dimensional Reconstruction from Radiographs and Electron Micrographs: Application of Convolutions Instead of Fourier Transforms." Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America 68 (1971): 2235-40.
  Ramachandran, G. N. and A. V. Lakshminarayanan. "Three-Dimensional Reconstruction from Radiographs and Electron Micrographs: Part III--Description and Application of the Convolution Method." Indian Journal of Pure and Applied Physics 9 (November 1971): 997-1003.
  Rhee, H. "A Representation of the Solutions of the Darboux Equation in Odd-Dimensional Spaces." Transactions of the American Mathematical Society 150 (August 1970): 491-98.
  Rohrlich, F. "The Equations of Motion of Classical Charges." Annals of Physics 13/1 (April 1961): 93-109.
  Rolnick, William B. and R. M. Thaler. "Relativistic Scattering of Two Equal-Mass Charged Particles." Physical Review Letters 14/14 (April 5, 1965): 572-74.
  Schiff, L. I. "Nuclear Multipole Transitions in Inelastic Electron Scattering." The Physical Review 96/3 (November 1, 1954): 765-72.
  Schopper, Herwig. "Kernresonanzstreuung von Gamma-Strahlen an V51." Zeitschrift fur Physik (1956): 476-87.
  Selove, W. and J. M. Teem. "Measurements of the Interaction of 95-MeV Protons with He4." The Physical Review 112/5 (December 1, 1958): 1658-66.
  Sezan, M. I. and H. Stark. "Image Restoration by the Method of Convex Projections: Part 2--Applications and Numerical Results." IEEE Transactions on Medical Imaging MI-1/2 (October 1982): 95-101.
  Sharpe, J. and G. H. Stafford. "The 12C(n,2n)11C Reaction in Anthracene Crystal." Proceedings of the Physical Society, A, vol. LXIV (1951): 211-12.
  Shepp, L. A., Y. Vardi, J. B. Ra, S. K. Hilal, and Z. H. Cho. "Maximum Likelihood PET With Real Data." IEEE Transactions on Nuclear Science NS-31/2 (April 1984): 910-13.
  Sherwin, C. W., H. Frauenfelder, E. L. Garwin, E. Luscher, S. Margulies, and R. N. Peacock. "Search for the Anisotropy of Inertia Using the Mossbauer Effect in Fe57." Physical Review Letters 4/8 (April 15, 1960): 399-104.
  Skilling, J. and R. K. Bryan. "Maximum Entropy Image Reconstruction: General Algorithm." Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society 211 (1984): 111-24.
  Smith, Kennan T, Donald C. Solmon, and Sheldon L. Wagner. "Practical and Mathematical Aspects of the Problem of Reconstructing Objects from Radiographs." Bulletin of the American Mathematical Society 83/6 (November 1977): 1227-70.
  Smith, P. R., T. M. Peters, and R. H. T. Bates. "Image Reconstruction from Finite Numbers of Projections." Journal of Physics A: Mathematical, Nuclear, and General 6 (March 1973): 361-82.
  Smith, P. R., T. M. Peters, H. R. Muller, and M. Elke. "Towards the Assessment of the Limitations on Computerized Axial Tomography." Neuroradiology 9 (1975): 1-8. Solmon, Donald C. "Asymptotic Formulas for the Dual Radon Transform and Applications." Mathematische Zeitschrift, 195 (1987): 321-44.
  Sommerfield, Charles M. "Tomographic Representations of Quantized Fields." In Bars, Chodos, Tze, eds., Symmetries in Particle Physics, New York: Plenum Press, 1984: 127-30.
  Stafford, G. H. "The Total Cross Section of Beryllium, Aluminum, Sulphur and Lead for Neutrons of Energies from 2MeV. To 6 MeV." Proceedings of the Physical Society, A, vol. LXIV (1951): 388-95.
  Stapp, H. P., T. J. Ypsilantis, and N. Metropolis. "Phase-Shift Analysis of 310-MeV Proton-Proton Scattering Experiments." The Physical Review 105/1 (January 1, 1957): 302-10.
  Stoy, R. H. "Standard Magnitudes at -45 Degree Declination." Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society 6 (1944): 288-328.
  Strauch, Karl. "Double Scattering Experiment with 96-MeV Protons." The Physical Review 99/1 (July 1, 1955): 150-54.
  Strauch, Karl. "On the Detection of High Energy Particles with a Fast Coincidence System." The Review of Scientific Instruments 24/4 (April 1953): 283-89.
  Strauch, K. and W. F. Titus. "Scattering of 96-Mev Protons from Light Nuclei. The Physical Review 95/3 (August 1, 1954): 854-55.
  Tanaka, Eiichi. "Generalized Correction Functions for Convolutional Techniques in Three-Dimensional Image Reconstruction." Physics of Medicine and Biology 24/1 (1979): 157-161.
  Taylor, A. E., E. Wood, and L. Bird. "Proton-Proton Scattering at 98 and 142 MeV." Nuclear Physics 16 (1960): 320-30.
  Taylor, Jeanne and William Parrish. "Absorption and Counting-Efficiency Data for X-Ray Detectors." The Review of Scientific Instruments 26/4 (April 1955): 367-73.
  Thomson, J. H. and J. E. B. Ponsonby. "Two-Dimensional Aperture Synthesis in Lunar Radar Astronomy." Proceedings of the Royal Society, A, vol. 303 (1968): 477-91.
  Tietz, T. "Uber eine Approximation der Fermischen Verteilungsfunktion." Annalen der Physik (1955): 186-188.
  Tretiak, Oleh and Charles Metz. "The Exponential Radion Transform." Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics Journal of Applied Mathematics 39/2 (October 1980): 341-54.
  Tuy, Heang. "Reconstruction of a Three-Dimensional Object from a Limited Range of Views." Journal of Mathematical Analysis and Applications 80 (1981): 598-616.
  Tyren, H., Peter Hillman, and A. Johnsson. "The Polarization of 173 MeV Protons INelastically Scattered by Carbon." Nuclear Physics 3 (1957): 336-39.
  Tyren, H., Peter Hillman, and Th. A. J. Maris. "High Energy (p, 2p) Reactions and Proton Binding Energies." Nuclear Physics 7/1 (1958): 10-23.
  Tyren, H and Th. A. J. Maris. "Inelastic Scattering of 185 MeV Protons on Oxygen, Calcium, and Carbon." Nuclear Physics 4/5 (1957): 637-42.
  Tyren, H and Th. A. J. Maris. "Studies of Inelastic Scattering of 185 MeV Protons on Carbon." Nuclear Physics 3 (1957): 52-59.
  Vainshtein, B. K. and S. S. Orlov. "Theory of the Recovery of Functions from Their Projections." Soviet Physics-Crystallography 17/2 (September-October 1972): 213-16.
  Wilson, Richard. "Nuclear Parameters in the Scattering of Nucleons by Carbon." The Physical Review 114/1 (April 1, 1959): 260-67.
  Wolfenstein, L. "Polarization of Fast Nucleons." Annual Review of Nuclear Science 6 (1956): 43-75.
  Zeitler, E. "The Reconstruction of Objects from Their Projections." Optik 39/4 (1971): 396-415.
  Arranged alphabetically by author.
  - A, 1960; MS018.007.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - B, 1979 -- 1985; MS018.007.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - C, 1931 -- 1985; MS018.007.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - D, 1977 -- 1979; MS018.007.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - E, 1974 -- 1980; MS018.007.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - F, 1970 -- 1981; MS018.007.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - G, 1957 -- 1990; MS018.007.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - H, 1968 -- 1984; MS018.007.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - J, 1965 -- 1979; MS018.007.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - K, 1962 -- 1989; MS018.007.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - L, 1957 -- 1968; MS018.007.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - M, 1966 -- 1980; MS018.007.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - N, 1978; MS018.007.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - O, 1960; MS018.007.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - P, 1978; MS018.007.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Q, 1983 -- 1990; MS018.007.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - R, 1941 -- 1980; MS018.007.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - S, 1973 -- 1982; MS018.007.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - T, 1969 -- 1986; MS018.007.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - V, 1980 -- 1984; MS018.007.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - W, 1968 -- 1982; MS018.007.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Z, 1974 -- 1980; MS018.007.014.00022 (Box 14)
- Photographs, 1979 -- 1986; MS018.008; 0.25 Linear Feet
  This series contains photographs, provided primarily by the Office of Communications and Public Relations, depicting Allan Cormack.
  - Photographs, 1979 -- 1986; MS018.008.016.00001 (Box 16)
    Two Photographs of Allan Cormack One copyrighted by Walter S. Silver, other by Seth Resnick c 1989